Guide to the Peter Reddaway Samizdat collection, 1950-2010 GRC0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Psychiatric Abuse, Circa 1960s to Circa 2010s; Series 7
  - Foreign Opposition Groups International Organizations, Series 7 Subseries 4
    - W[orld] P[sychiatric] A[ssociation] Newsletters etc., 1971 November 11-1987; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Belgium, Canada, Austria, Holland, Germany [1/4], 1981 May 15-1990 September 6; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Belgium, Canada, Austria, Holland, Germany [2/4], 1977 September 3-1982 October 1; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Belgium, Canada, Austria, Holland, Germany [3/4], 1977 June 22-1979 June 20; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Belgium, Canada, Austria, Holland, Germany [4/4], 1971 January 19-1977 April 21; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Betsy [US Delegation to Soviet Psychiatric Hospitals] [1/2], 1989 February 10-1989 July 16; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Betsy [US Delegation to Soviet Psychiatric Hospitals] [2/2], 1988 January 4-1989 June 9; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Deutsche Vereinigung gegen politischen MiBbrauch der Psychiatrie, 1998 May; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - French Activities [1/2], 1976 July 25-1985 April 10; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - French Activities [2/2], 1971 August 23-1976 December; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Geneva Initative on Psychiatry - Report on the 10th world congress and the fourth meeting of reformers in phsychiatry, 1996 August; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Geneva Initative on Psychiatry [GIP] Annual Reports, 1997-2002; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Geneva Initative on Psychiatry; Translation Database, 1997-1998; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - GIP - Political Psychiatry in China: A First Glance at the Documentary Evidence, undated; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - GIP Documents/1 Judicial Psychiatry in China and its Political Abuses, undated; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - GIP Press-clippings from Rumania, Attacks on Tuculescu C.S. [Dr. Tuculescu on a "Rumanian Psychiatric Gulag"], 1992 March; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Guide to the Program for Participants from Central Eastern Europe and the CIS - World Congress of Psychiatry, Madrid Special Sessions, 1996 August 23; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Mental Health Reforms - Documents on the Abolition and Prevention of Abuse of Psychiatry, A Geneva Initiative on Psychiatry Publication [1/4], 2002-2003; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Mental Health Reforms - Documents on the Abolition and Prevention of Abuse of Psychiatry, A Geneva Initiative on Psychiatry Publication [2/4], 2000-2001; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Mental Health Reforms - Documents on the Abolition and Prevention of Abuse of Psychiatry, A Geneva Initiative on Psychiatry Publication [3/4], 1998-1999; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health Reforms - Documents on the Abolition and Prevention of Abuse of Psychiatry, A Geneva Initiative on Psychiatry Publication [4/4], 1997; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Plyushch Committee [-Internatinal Committee of Mathematicians for the Defense of Leonid Plyushch; Bulletins 1-8], 1972-1975; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - [Psychiatric Abuse], 1977 August 5-1985 May; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Psychiatric Abuse - World Psychiatric Association [1/4], 1979 January 10-1983 July 16; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Psychiatric Abuse - World Psychiatric Association [2/4], 1977 August 29-1984 October 19; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Psychiatric Abuse - World Psychiatric Association [3/4], 1974 November 19-1978 January; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Psychiatric Abuse - World Psychiatric Association [4/4], 1971 June 2-1976 August 23; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - [Punitive Psychiatry], undated; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Strategic Policy Paper - Long-term Plans of Geneva Initiative on Psychiatry [and] Furthering Mental Health Reform in Central Eastern Europe the New Independent States, 1998 May; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Switzerland [1/2], 1976 October 28-1987 April 10; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Switzerland [2/2], 1973 May 11-1977 April 5; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - USA [1/2], 1987 November 5-1991 September 16; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - USA [2/2], 1987 January 12-1987 August 19; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - USA (Cont[inue]d) [1/4], 1985 March 27-1986 December 26; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - USA (Cont[inue]d) [2/4], 1984 June 18-1985 April 26; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - USA (Cont[inue]d) [3/4], 1982 January 26-1984 June 29; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - USA (Cont[inue]d) [4/4], 1983 February 1-1984 July 6; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - USA Activities [1/4], 1980 December 31-1983 April 7; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - USA Activities [2/4], 1978 October 20-1980 April 10; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - USA Activities [3/4], 1976 January 7-1978 December 3; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - USA Activities [4/4], 1970 October 18-1976 August 23; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Miscellanea, Series 7 Subseries 5
    - Amnesty and Soviet Dissidents Current [Various Psychiatric Abuse Materials], 1975 October 8-1977 July 21; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Commentary [articles and clippings], 1985 December 12-1987 November 1; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Koryagin's Psych[iatric] Reports in R[ussia]n Engl[ish] his articles m[aterial]s [1/3], 1979 December 5-1988 June 27; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Koryagin's Psych[iatric] Reports in R[ussia]n Engl[ish] his articles m[aterial]s [2/3], 1980 April 4-1982 March 18; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Koryagin's Psych[iatric] Reports in R[ussia]n Engl[ish] his articles m[aterial]s [3/3], 1972-1985 July 23; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [1/14], 1984-1990 May 29; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [2/14], 1962 September-1977 May 3; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [3/14], 1969-2000 January 9; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [4/14], 1988 January 4-1998 July 24; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [5/14], 1987 December 16-1995 August 13; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [6/14], 1971 March 16-1992 September 18; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [7/14], 1989 September 23-1991 September 20; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [8/14], 1989 May 22-1991 June 11; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [9/14], 1989 August-1990 October 22; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [10/14], 1988 March 6-1991 May 4; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [11/14], 1969-1990 November 5; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [12/14], 1987 March 21-1989 October 19; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [13/14], 1987 June 29-1988 October 28; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - [Miscellanea in Human Rights and Psychiatry] [14/14], 1987 June 29-1988 June 12; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Miscellanea Psychiatry, 1971 November 4-1977 October 30; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Other Countries [1/4], 1982-1990 March 3; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Other Countries [2/4], 1981 July 3-1985 March 28; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Other Countries [3/4], 1979 May 15-1982 November 25; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Other Countries [4/4], 1968 April 2-1981 June; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - [Psych Abuse Press Materials (mostly Soviet)] [1/2], 1987 October 24-1988 April 27; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - [Psych Abuse Press Materials (mostly Soviet)] [2/2], 1987 January 26-1987 December 27; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - [Psychiatric Abuse], 1989 February 10-1989 September 21; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Psych[iatric] Abuse - Various Doc[ument]s [1/4], 1987 February 11-1989 September 18; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Psych[iatric] Abuse - Various Doc[ument]s [2/4], 1987 November 25-1989 October 13; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Psych[iatric] Abuse - Various Doc[ument]s [3/4], 1988 June 30-1989 August 8; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Psych[iatric] Abuse - Various Doc[ument]s [4/4], 1989 January 11-1990 October 18; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Psych[iatric] Abuse Bibliography, 1969 July 23-1985 June 18; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - [Psychiatric Abuse Monitoring and Reports], 1989 March 28-1989 May 1; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Psychiatry - Soviet Official Activities [1/4], 1983 February 25-1992 June 10; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Psychiatry - Soviet Official Activities [2/4], 1976 January 30-1983 August 19; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Psychiatry - Soviet Official Activities [3/4], 1974-1977 October 27; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Psychiatry - Soviet Official Activities [4/4], 1967 October 10-1976 February 28; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Psychiatry - Unsorted [1/5], 1987 January 5-2000; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Psychiatry - Unsorted [2/5], 1980 May 5-1980 June 4; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Psychiatry - Unsorted [3/5], 1984-1991 August 28; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Psychiatry - Unsorted [4/5], 1972 February 14-1992 November 5; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Psychiatry - Unsorted [5/5], 1977 March 22-1983 November 30; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Psychiatry History, 1927-1984 January; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Psychiatry Law, 1967 November 14-1973 January 12; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - USSR: Appeals, Inf[ormation] on PHs, victims, Psychiatrists etc. [1/2], 1978 July 13-1988 May 26; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - USSR: Appeals, Inf[ormation] on PHs, victims, Psychiatrists etc. [2/2], 1970 May-1979 February 26; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Various Psych[iatric] Abuse materials, 1981 March 15-2010 February; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - White book on the Internment of Dissenters in Soviet Mental Hospitals, undated; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Working Commission on Psych[iatric] Abuse (Moscow) 1978-79 [1/3], 1978 July 20-1980 April 27; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Working Commission on Psych[iatric] Abuse (Moscow) 1978-79 [2/3], 1977 September 13-1978 September 15; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Working Commission on Psych[iatric] Abuse (Moscow) 1978-79 [3/3], 1977 June 8-1978 July 20; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Working Commission to Investigate the Use of Psychiatry for Political Purposes (Moscow) 1980 -> [1/2], 1979 February 15-1983 December 12; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Working Commission to Investigate the Use of Psychiatry for Political Purposes (Moscow) 1980 -> [2/2], 1978 June 30-1982 August 25; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [1/5], 1978 February 12-1988 June 8; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [2/5], 1976 September 20-1982; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [3/5], 1971 February 18-1976 September 20; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [4/5], 1971 August 17-1977 June; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [5/5], 1974 October 6-1978 June 10; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [1/3], 1972 October 6-1976 February 18; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [2/3], 1971 March 11-1973 December 29; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Working Group [on the Internment of Dissenters in Mental Hospitals] [3/3], 1970 July 15-1984 July 1; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 147, Folder 5)
- Religious, Circa 1960s to Circa 1990; Series 8
  Contains a variety of documents illustrating the struggle for the freedom of religion in the USSR. It contains documents produced in the USSR and abroad, such as the Christian Baptist bulletin, Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania, Religion and Atheism in USSR, Keston News Bulletins and others. It documents the struggle of Soviet Baptists, Catholics, Orthodox Christians, Pentecostals, Adventists, Muslims. It contains documents on persecutions of Soviet Buddhologists.
  Organized into five subseries: Bulletin, Collective, Foreign Oppositions and International Organizations, Journal, Miscellanea
  - Bulletin, Series 8 Subseries 1
    - [Christian ]BAP[tists] Bull[etin]s [1/2], 1977; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - [Christian ]BAP[tists] Bull[etin]s [2/2], 1976; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania - no.4-23; no.26-69; no.71-79 [1/6], 1972-1977; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania - no.4-23; no.26-69; no.71-79 [2/6], 1978; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania - no.4-23; no.26-69; no.71-79 [3/6], 1978-1980 July 30; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania - no.4-23; no.26-69; no.71-79 [4/6], 1980 October 22-1981 December 8; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania - no.4-23; no.26-69; no.71-79 [5/6], 1983 April 3-1985 April 7; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania - no.4-23; no.26-69; no.71-79 [6/6], 1985 July 16-1988 September 8; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania - no.70, 1986 April 23; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Herald of Repression in Ukraine, no.1-7; no.10-12, 1980-1981; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Keston News Service [1/2], 1974 May 17-1977 January 13; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Keston News Service [2/2], 1977 February 3-1978 December 6; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Religious Prisoners in the USSR - Keston College, 1987; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [1/8], 1981 December-1984 September; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [2/8], 1980 May-1983 March; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [3/8], 1978 June-1980 April; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [4/8], 1976 July-1978 May; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [5/8], 1974 August-1976 June; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [6/8], 1971 November-1974 July; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [7/8], 1969 October-1971 September; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Religiya I Ateizm v SSSR [8/8], 1967 November-1969 August; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - The C[hristian] C[ommittee for the] D[efense of] B[elievers] R[ights in the USSR] Documents [-Vol. XIII], 1982; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Collective, Series 8 Subseries 2
    - Adventistis (7th Day) [1/2], 1980 August 11-1984 September; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Adventistis (7th Day) [2/2], 1980 July 24-1981 June 1; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Adventists, 1975 June 8-1975 September 4; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Adventists (7th Day) ? [1/3], 1979 March 15-1979 November 18; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Adventists (7th Day) ? [2/3], 1978 March 17-1979 February 18; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Adventists (7th Day) ? [3/3], 1976 February 9-1978 March 14; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Baptists [1/2], 1978 February 20-1987 May 29; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Baptists [2/2], 1977 April 4-1983 January 17; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Baptists [1/2], 1971 June 5-1976 December 5; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Baptists [2/2], 1973 January 29-1974 March31; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Baptists, 1967 September; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Baptists [1/3], 1965 July-1973 March; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Baptists [2/3], 1969 March 20-1971 May 27; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Baptists [3/3], 1970 November 19-1973 January 26; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Buddhologists, 1972 October 22-1975 March 12; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Catholics [1/3], 1970 June-1977 March 30; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Catholics [2/3], 1974 December 31-1975 February 14; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Catholics [3/3], 1971 November 12-1974; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - [Chris]tian Committee to Defend Believers' Rights, 1977 February 7-1981 June 21; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Lithuanians + Catholics [1/2], 1977 November 8-1980 November 7; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Lithuanians + Catholics [2/2], 1971 March 12-1977 August 3; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Lithuanians + Catholics, 1980 January 17-1991 February 10; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Muslims, 1978 October 26-1988 September 28; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Obviaitel'noe zakliuchenie po dely BSHKSON-a, 1968-1973; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Obviaitel'noe zakliuchenie po dely BSHKSON-a, 1968-1973; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Orthodox [1/2], 1969 May-1977 July 18; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Orthodox [2/2], 1968 November 4-1969 September 26; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Other Religions + Sects [1/2], 1974 August 15-1977 February 24; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Other Religions + Sects [2/2], 1974 February 25-1975 April 23; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Pentecostalists [1/2], 1977 September 3-1979 December12; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Pentecostalists [2/2], 1976 May 13-1979 May 6; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Pentecostalists [1/3], 1983 February 1-1988 November 11; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Pentecostalists [2/3], 1980 January 28-1983 January 27; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Pentecostalists [3/3], 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Russian Orthodox [1/3], 1983 November-1990 August 30; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Russian Orthodox [2/3], 1980 January 1-1983 August 17; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Russian Orthodox [3/3], 1976 November 11-1983 August 29; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - SHB (I) [Soviet Baptists] 301(2), 1963 August 13-1972 December 16; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - SHB (I) [Soviet Baptists] 302 [1/3], 1968 April 26-1974 June 16; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - SHB (I) [Soviet Baptists] 302 [2/3], 1969 November 20-1972 March 29; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - SHB (I) [Soviet Baptists] 302 [3/3], 1966 July 7-1970 March 13; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Social-Christians (L[enin]grad), 1974 July 21-1977 February 19; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Ukrainian Catholics, 1984 September 8-1985 October 14; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Unlabeled [Baptists] [1/2], 1972 December 13-1984 March 1; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Unlabeled [Baptists] [2/2], 1969 February 28-1971 July 9; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Opposition Groups and International Organizations, Series 8 Subseries 3
    - An Appeal for Religious Freedom in the Soviet Union on the Occasion of the Millenium of Christianity in Kievan Rus' -The James Madison Foundation, 1989; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - C[entre for the] S[tudy of] R[eligion and] C[ommunism] [1/6], 1969 July 16-1978 September 27; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - C[entre for the] S[tudy of] R[eligion and] C[ommunism] [2/6], 1983 October 4-2011 September 7; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - C[entre for the] S[tudy of] R[eligion and] C[ommunism] [3/6], 1929 May 15-1989 January 17; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - C[entre for the] S[tudy of] R[eligion and] C[ommunism] [4/6], 1983 June 21-1986 September 26; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - C[entre for the] S[tudy of] R[eligion and] C[ommunism] [5/6], 1983 March-1984 September 5; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - C[entre for the] S[tudy of] R[eligion and] C[ommunism] [6/6], 1975 August 17-1984 September 10; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Communist Exploitation of Religion [Hearing before the Subcommittee to Investigate the Administration of the Security Act and other Security Laws - Testimony of Rev. Richard Wurmbrand], 1966 May 6; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Final Documents of the World Conference: Religious Workers for Lasting Peace, disarmaments and just relations among nations, Moscow, 1977 June 6; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Persecution of Relgion in Ukraine, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Translation Service (Baptists, mainly), 1974 October 31-1976 May 24; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Journal, Series 8 Subseries 4
    - Chronicle of the Catholic Church in Lithuania 4-23, 26-69, 71-79, 1979 January 6; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Documents of the Christian Committee for the Defense of believers' rights in the USSR - Vol.2, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Documents of the Christian Committee for the Defense of believers' rights in the USSR - Vol.3, 1977-1978; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Documents of the Christian Committee for the Defense of believers' rights in the USSR - Vol.4, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Documents of the Christian Committee for the Defense of believers' rights in the USSR - Vol.5:no.1, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 123, Folder 1)